Guide to the Jerome H. Holland papers, 1953-1985
Holland, Jerome H. papers, 1953-1985
- Series I. Professional Files
  - Speech: Milwaukee Society, "Implications in Higher Education", March 3, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 84)
  - Speech: "A Mirror of Hope," Jacksonville, FL, February 14, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 85)
  - Speech: Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 86)
  - Speech: Mount Hermon School Student-Faculty Forum, November 8, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 87)
  - Speech: National Broadcasting System, "The Educational Status of the Negro", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 88)
  - Speech: National Council of Jewish Women, April 23, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 89)
  - Speech: National League of Nursing, Louisville, KY, Ocotber 5, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 90)
  - Speech: National League of Nursing, "The Administrative Responsibility in the Senior College/University in Nursing Education", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 91)
  - Speech: Naval Weapons Station Management Organization, December 9, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 92)
  - Speech: New Hope Baptist Church, May 19, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 93)
  - Speech: New York City, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 94)
  - Speech: North Atlantic Regional Conference, October 14, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 95)
  - Speech: Northeastern States Youth Citizenship Conference, Tufts University, MA, June 6, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 96)
  - Speech: Parent Teachers' Association, Salem, NJ, March 12, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 97)
  - Speech: Parents and Teachers Meeting, Newport News, VA, September 30, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 98)
  - Speech: Paul Lawrence Dunbar School, Laurel, Delaware, October 16, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 99)
  - Speech: Phenix High School, Hampton, VA, June 15, 1962, January 12, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Speech: Phi Delta Kappa Regional, Wilmington, Delaware, May 28, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 101)
  - Speech: Philadelphia Urban League, November 20, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 102)
  - Speech: Pierre S. Dupont High School, February 5, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 103)
  - Speech: Pinkett, Gordon H. Funeral Services, June 29, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 104)
  - Speech: Progressive Community Center, December 13, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 105)
  - Speech: Progressive Recreation and Social Service Association Dedication, September 29, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 106)
  - Speech: RCA Corporation, Executive's Meeting, February 18, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Speech: Rotary Club of New York, September 21, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Speech: San Diego Urban League, February 15, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Speech: "Socio-Economic Implications in Manpower Training," Racine, Wisconsin, February 6-7, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Speech: "Some Problems in Intercollegiate Athletics", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Speech: South Carolina State Legislature, Black Caucus, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Speech: St. Joseph's College Commencement Program, N. Windham, Maine, June 6, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Speech: St. Paul Urban League, January 21, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Speech: State Vocational and Practical Arts Teachers, June 25, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Speech: Student Leadership Institute, September 12, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Speech: Sussex County Education Association, March 1959 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Speech: Symposium on the High Cost of Population, New York City, October 16, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 118)
  - Speech: Texas Southern University, Men's Council, April 25, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Speech: 32nd Degree Masons, Philadelphia, PA, October 18, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 120)
  - Speech: Unity Club Meeting, March 27, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 121)
  - Speech: University of Delaware, March 1954, July 1959 (Box 19, Folder 122)
  - Speech: Urban League of Greater St. Louis, March 10, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 123)
  - Speech: Virginia Federation of Parents and Teachers, December 7, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 124)
  - Speech: Virginia Teacher's Association, Richmond, Virginia, November 2, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 125)
  - Speech: W.D.E.L Radio, December 5, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 126)
  - Speech: W.H.O.V., "Value of Radio to the College and Surrounding Community," Hampton, Virginia, March 11, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 127)
  - Speech: Wall Street: Past, Present, and Future, March 5, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 128)
  - Speech: Warren, Ohio Urban League Annual Meeting, January 21, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 129)
  - Speech: Wesley Junior College Assembly, May 4, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Speech: West Philadelphia High School Laureati Assembly, June 3, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 131)
  - Speech: Westchester Community Center, April 30, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Speech: Westminister Presbyterian Church, Women's Group, June 3, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Speech: Whatcoat Methodist Church, Dover, Delaware, March 21, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 134)
  - Speech: William Henry High School, Dover, Delaware, June 1954 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Speech: William Jason High School, April 14, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Speech: William Penn Business School's Commencement Exercises, August 9, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Speech: William Penn High School, New Castle, Delaware, December 4, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Speech: Williamsburg International Assembly, June 10, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Speech: Williamsburg Recreation Center, Virginia, April 30, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - Speech: Women of G.A.R., Wilmington, Delaware, February 12, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - Speech: Woman's Society of Christian Service Conference, July 20, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - Speech File Index, 1953-1970 (Box 19, Folder 143)
  - Speech File Index, 1973-1983 (Box 19, Folder 144)
  - Speech Materials, 1916-1964 (Box 19, Folder 145)
  - Speech Materials, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 146)
  - Speech Materials, 1967-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Speech materials: Cornell, 1940-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Speech materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Speech materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Speech materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sports Illustrated Silver Anniversary All American, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Spring Mills, 1976-1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Spring Mills: Minority Trade Fair Banquet, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Star Social Club, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - State Department Briefing, 1963-1970, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Study of Negro Vote, 1952 Presidential Elections, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Sun Oil Company, 1945-1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company, 1942-1944 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sun Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Company, 1945-1963 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Super Bowl IX, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Swedish Church, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Swedish Society of New York, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Systems Management American, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - T: General, 1952-1982, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Taylor, Oliver G., 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee State University, 1945-1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Tennessee State University: Howard C. Gentry Complex, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Testimonial dinner for Jerome Holland, Dec. 16, 1937, 1937-1938 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Testimonial dinner for Jerome Holland, Dec. 8, 1943, Nov.-Dec. 1943 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Testimonial dinner for Jerome Holland, March 23, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Testimonial dinner for Jerome Holland, Feb. 14 and Mar. 10, 1970, Jan.-Mar. 10, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Testimonial dinner for Jerome Holland, Feb.14 and Mar. 10, 1970, Mar. 11-18, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Thanks to Scandinavia, Inc., 1974-1983 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Touchdown Club, 1954-1973 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Touche Ross & Co., 1973-1984 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Transvaal Chamber of Industries, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Tri-Esso Club, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Trip to Sweden, Sept.21-26, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Tuskegee Institute, 1952-1981 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Twenty-First Century Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - U: General, 1944-1969 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - U: General, 1973-1983, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - U.S.O, War Department-Troop Morale, 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, Jan.-Apr.il 1976 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, May-Dec.1976 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Union Carbide Corporation, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Union Carbid Corporation: Trips, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Union Carbide Corporation:South Africa and Rhodesia, 1975, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Union League Club, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Union College, February-May 1966 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1947-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - United Negro College Fund: Eastern Pennsylvania Campaign Kick-off, September 29, 1981, Sept. 1981-March 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - United Negro College Fund: Speeches, 1953-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - United Negro College Fund: Speeches, 1975-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - United States Congress: Correspondence, 1944-1945, 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - United States-Japan Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - United States Jaycee's, December 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - United States National Olympic Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - United States Postal Service, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - United States Senate: Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - United States Trust Company, 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - United Way, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - University of Cincinnati: Honorary Doctor of Law, June 10, 1966, June 1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - University of Delaware, 1955-1959 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - University of Missouri, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1946-1959 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1960-1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - University of South Carolina: Visiting Lecturer, 1982-April 1983 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - University of South Carolina: Visiting Lecturer, April 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - University of the South, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - University System of Georgia, Colored Division, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Urban National Corporation, 1976-1983 (Folder 21, Box 23)
  - V: General, 1944-1983 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Villa Maria College, March-May 1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Virgin Islands: Correspondence with Dr. A. C. Preston, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Virgin Islands: Ford Foundation Public Administration, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Commission on the Arts and Humanities, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Commission on the Arts and Humanities: Materials, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Commission on the Arts and Humanities: Materials, 1966, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Cultural Development Commission, 1966-Apr.il 1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Cultural Development Commission, May 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, July 3-15, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, July 23-Sept. 1969 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Union, 1952-1973, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Virginia Woman's Forum, April-November 1980 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Voorhees College, Denmark, S.C., 1962, 1973, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - W: General, 1950-1975 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - W: General, 1976-1983, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Walker, Mel: Kraft Foods, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - War Food Administration, January-March 1944, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Ward Howell Associates, October 1973, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Washington University, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Washington and Lee University, 1973-1983, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Weybright and Talley, Inc., publishers, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Weybright and Talley, Inc., publishers, Jan.-Feb. 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Weybright and Talley, Inc., publishers, Mar. 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - White House: Correspondence, 1966-1985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Who's Who, 1963-1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Williams, Clarence (MIT), 1972-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Williams, Clarence (MIT), 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Clarence (MIT), 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Clarence (MIT), 1978-1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Willing Worker's Society, February 1, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, 1974-1976, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - World Brotherhood, November 1952-February 1953 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - World Energy Conference: Detroit, Michigan, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - X-Z: General, 1944-1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - YMCA, 1945-1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - YMCA, 1974-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - YMCA: Unity Club, 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Young President's Organization: Trip to Greece, May 11-17, 1975, 1974-May 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Young President's Organization: Trip to Greece, May 11-17, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Young President's Organization: Trip to Greece, May 11-17, 1975, May-September, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Zurn Industries, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Zurn Industries, Inc., 19778-1984 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Series II. Writings
  - Delaware State College Writings
    - An Analysis of the Patterns of Negro Residency in the State of Delaware, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - An Appraisal of the Health of the Delaware Negro, 1916-1955, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - New Horizons in Guidance for Minority-Group Youth, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - A Sociological Analysis of the Situational Complex Confronting the State of Delaware Relative to Implementing the Desegregation-Integration of the Public Schools, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - A Study of the Employment Status of the Negro Population in the State of Delaware, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - President's Report and Remarks, Hampton Institute
    - President's Report, Hampton Institute, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - President's Report, Hampton Institute, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - President's Report, Hampton Institute: "A Mirror of Hope: The President's Report for the First Five Years, 1960-61 - 1964-65", 1965 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report of the President, Hampton Institute, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Annual Report of the President, Hampton Institute, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Reports and remarks to the Board of Trustees, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Other Writings
    - Black Opportunity manuscript, pgs. iii-69, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Black Opportunity manuscript, pgs. 70-124, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Black Opportunity manuscript, pgs. 125-189, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Black Opportunity manuscript, pgs. 190-249, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Black Opportunity manuscript, pgs. 250-316, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Black Opportunity, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - "A Challenge in Leadership," Associated Press Story, March 1961 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "The Community and the Ghetto," reprinted from Alumnae Journal, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "Identifying the Barriers to the Spread of Knowledge about Family Planning with Suggestions for their Reduction or Elimination," Essay Competition, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - The Negro and Higher Education, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New Frontiers for America's Private Colleges, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - "A Study of Negros Employed by the Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company During World War II and their Problems in the Post War Period," Jerome H. Holland Ph.D., 1950 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Svart framtid? Om Negrernas mojligheter i framtidens varld, Jerome H. Holland., 1970 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - "Time to Pause", n.d. (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Series III. Condolences
  - Letters of condolence: A, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Letters of condolence: B, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Letters of condolence: B, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Letters of condolence: B, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Letters of condolence: C, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Letters of condolence: C, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Letters of condolence: D, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Letters of condolence: E, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Letters of condolence: F, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Letters of condolence: G, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Letters of condolence: H, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Letters of condolence: H, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Letters of condolence: H, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Letters of condolence: I, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Letters of condolence: J, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Letters of condolence: J, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Letters of condolence: K, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Letters of condolence: L, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Letters of condolence: M, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Letters of condolence: M, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Letters of condolence: N, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Letters of condolence: O, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Letters of condolence: P, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Letters of condolence: R, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Letters of condolence: S, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Letters of condolence: S, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Letters of condolence: T, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Letters of condolence: U-V, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Letters of condolence: W, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Letters of condolence: W, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Letters of condolence: W, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Letters of condolence: Y, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Letters of condolence: Z, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Letters of condolence: No last name signed, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Letters of condolence: No last name signed, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Letters of condolence: No last name signed, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Thank you letters: A-F, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Thank you letters: G-J, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Thank you letters: K-M, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Thank you letters: N-R, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Thank you letters: S-Z, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Series IV. Sweden (Embassy)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, January 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, February 1970 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, March 1970 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, March 1970 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, March 1970 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, March 1970 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Sweden, April 1970 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Sweden, May 1970 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, June 1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, July 1970 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, August 1970 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Sweden, September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Sweden, October 1970 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Sweden, October 1970 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Sweden, October 1970 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Sweden, October 1970 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Sweden, October 1970 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Sweden, November 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, November 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, November 1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, November 1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, December 1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sweden: Clippings, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sweden: Planner, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, January 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, January 1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, January 1971 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, January 1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, February 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, February 1971 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, February 1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, February 1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, February 1971 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, March 1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, March 1971 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Sweden, March 1971 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, March 1971 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Sweden, March 1971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Sweden: Photographs, March 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Sweden: Photographs, March 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, May 1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, June 1971 (Box 27, Folder 19)